Hey Gas,
so I'm going to start this video with
health insurance.
As you all know, health
insurance is becoming very important in today's life.
However, I want
everyone in every family to have
health insurance.
I want to tell you something. As I was
checking today, I checked
about health insurance and they are providing
you health insurance at a very cheap premium.
But,
I would request you not to buy any health related product from
Navi or any other online provider
because you can face
problems in the future. And you do face them.
I have checked a lot of reviews. Those
who have taken health insurance from Naveen are facing a
lot of problems. They do
n't pass the test either. They don't take customer
care
or help you in any
way. In fact, the hospital people also
say that it's okay.
In the beginning, they say that we have
everything on our panel, but at the end, they do
n't support you in any way.
So, Gas, I want to  You should
not buy any product of Navi related to health insurance because there
is a big fraud in it and tomorrow you
and your family may face problems,
any problem may arise, so be safe, be
happy, thank you
[Music]